{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/2266","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2266","name":"Dish","address":"18441 Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48236","owner":"Paul F. Sulek","licenseNumber":"042577","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Temporarily Closed","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-82.91383,42.41023","geojson":{"id":"2266","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.91382899,42.4102301]},"properties":{"name":"Dish","owner":"Paul F. Sulek","address":"18441 Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48236","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"042577","establishmentid":"2266","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Temporarily Closed","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"12/5/2016"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622780","name":"Side Dish","address":"18441 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"4405","name":"McDonald's","address":"18201 Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"1595","name":"Rabaut's Cafe","address":"18536 Warren Ave. E.","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"1867","name":"GPCR Management Co.","address":"4831 Canyon Dr.","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"3040","name":"Robinson Dairy Vending","address":"18300 Warren E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"4586","name":"Total Vending","address":"18300 East Warren","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51623239","name":"Chipotle Mexican Grill #3692","address":"4444 Radnor","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"1264","name":"Calvary Senior Center","address":"4950 Gateshead","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3466","name":"Country Grill","address":"18051  Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"1018","name":"Country Inn","address":"18051 Mack Ave.","zipcode":"48224"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"41835","inspectionDate":"2018-04-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"QA Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"41054","inspectionDate":"2017-12-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"ceiling","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Around the Ceiling vent","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"WAITING AREA","subLocation":"Missing Coved molding","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."}]},{"inspectionid":"41529","inspectionDate":"2017-07-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"LOBBY/ (Customer Waiting Area)","subLocation":"Missing Coved molding","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Missing Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Condenser","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""}]},{"inspectionid":"39540","inspectionDate":"2017-07-20T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"LOBBY/ (Customer Waiting Area)","subLocation":"Missing Coved molding","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Condenser","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":""}]},{"inspectionid":"37835","inspectionDate":"2017-01-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-204.11","violationDescription":"Chemical SANITIZERS and other chemical antimicrobials applied to FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall meet the requirements specified in this code. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Sanitizer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not comply with law","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Bleach","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide labels that comply with law."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Condenser","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"LOBBY/ (Customer Waiting Area)","subLocation":"Missing Coved molding","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Certified Manager","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Grease extraction filters","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36101","inspectionDate":"2016-08-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Wall (back)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Under the Condenser","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Grease extraction filters","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2266"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}